

damien@romito.fr

iOS Developer

I am passionate about the world of Multimedia and especially about its social dimension and its interactivity. My challenge is to design and develop apps to bring the users to their most enjoyable and friendly experiences. Publisher : Damien Romito Released : 9 march 1989

Version: 2.0

Languages: fr, en, de

Customer service : (415)812-1025 Website : www.damienromito.fr More apps by Damien Romito:









Education

October 2011 - June 2012

3-year highter diploma equivalent to a graduate degree specialize in mobile on-line production

Design, development of iOs app & Cocos2D game Gobelins, Paris

September 2010 - June 2011

Bachelor of Computing Web development specialisation ESGI, Paris

September 2008 - June 2010

Interactive Media Designer 2-year highter diploma equivalent to a graduate degree specialize in digital on-line production La fonderie de l'image, Bagnolet

September 2007- May 2008

Foundation course in Art Visual Communication (multimedia specialisation)

La fonderie de l'image, Bagnolet

Work Experience

September 2012 - December 2013

iOS Developer

Onefeat, San Francisco/Paris

September 2011 - August 2012

Front-End Developer

BNP Paribas, Paris

September 2010 - August 2011

Front-End Developer

Milky Interactive, Paris

July 2010 - August 2010

Full Stack Developer and Graphic Designer

EGK Distribution, Avignon

July 2008 - June 2010

Web Developer and Web Designer

Inow SSII, Paris

June 2008

Flash Developer

Kino, Audiovisual Agency, Paris

Skills

Mobile

Web Client

Web Server

Objective-C

HTML5 / CCS3 / Javascript

Ruby

Basics: AS3, JAVA, C#/ASP, C, Bash.

Frameworks : Cocoa touch, Cocos 2D, Android, Symfony2, Ruby on Rails, Wordpress, Backbone, jQuery.

Favorite Tools: Xcode, Sublime Text 2, Github, Stackoverflow, Photoshop, Balsamiq.

Hobbies

Composer and musician of a band (quitar, piano), Improvisational theater, Capoeira.





